#### Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/samsirafi (LinkedIn)

#### Top Skills

Higher Education
Public Speaking
Research

# Sam Sirafi

**Data Scientist** 

Orange County, California Area

### Summary

Experienced Data Scientist with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in Python (Programming Language), Microsoft Word, Data Science, Public Speaking, and LaTeX. Strong engineering professional with a Master of Science (M.S.) focused in Statistics from California State University-Fullerton.

## Experience

Chipotle Mexican Grill Senior Data Scientist May 2019 - Present (11 months)

Panasonic Avionics Corporation
Data Scientist
May 2018 - May 2019 (1 year 1 month)
Lake Forest, California

Black Swan Data 2 years 1 month

Data Scientist/ Project Manager Hybrid role
July 2017 - May 2018 (11 months)

Orange County, California Area

Data Scientist May 2016 - May 2018 (2 years 1 month) Lake Forest, California

Tropicon Foods, Inc.
Office Administrator
June 2013 - May 2016 (3 years)

Earth Science Associates

Data Analysis - Graduate Student Project

Page 1 of 2

January 2015 - May 2015 (5 months)

California State University, Fullerton Teaching Associate August 2014 - May 2015 (10 months)

#### Education

California State University-Fullerton
Master of Science (M.S.), Statistics · (2015 - 2017)

California State University-Fullerton

Master's degree, Applied Mathematics · (2013 - 2015)

University of California, Santa Barbara Bachelor's, Mathematics (2008 - 2011)